conferencetm.com 2009-09-09

# ConferenceTM Privacy Statement

We are committed to providing you with the highest levels of customer service. This includes protecting your privacy.

This Privacy Policy covers conferenceTM's treatment of personally identifiable information that conferenceTM collects when you are on the conferenceTM's site, and when you use conferenceTM's services.

This policy also covers conferenceTM's treatment of any personally identifiable information that conferenceTM's business partners share with conferenceTM or that conferenceTM may collect on a partner's site. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that conferenceTM does not own or control, or to people that conferenceTM does not employ or manage.

##### _Information Collection and Use_  

conferenceTM collects personally identifiable information when you register for an conferenceTM account, when you use certain conferenceTM products or services, and when you enter promotions. conferenceTM may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.

When you register with conferenceTM, we ask for your name, email address, other contact details street address and telephone number details. Once you register with conferenceTM's and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

This site is operated by the conferenceTM using commercial web Hosting facilities. When visiting this site, a record of your visit is logged. The following information is recorded for statistical purposes and is used by conferenceTM to help improve the site. Thisinformation is supplied by your browser:

  * The user's server address 
  * The user's operating system (for example Windows, Mac etc) 
  * The user's top level domain name (for example .com, .gov, .au, .uk etc) 
  * The date and time of the visit to the site 
  * The pages accessed and the documents downloaded 
  * The previous site visited 
  * The type of browser used. 

No attempt will be made to identify users or their browsing activities except in the unlikely event of an investigation, where a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect the Internet web server logs.

##### _Information Sharing and Disclosure_  

conferenceTM will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. 

conferenceTM will only send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:  

  * We have your consent to share the information; 
  * We need to share your information in order to provide the product or Service you have requested; 
  * We need to send the information to companies that work on behalf of conferenceTM to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.); 

We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or We find that your actions on our web sites violate the conferenceTM Terms of Service \- which includes any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

##### _Security_  

Your conferenceTM Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. 

In certain areas conferenceTM uses industry-standard SSL-encryption To protect data transmissions.

##### _General Disclaimer_  

conferenceTM, its employees, officers and agents will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from use of the conferenceTM website, or any related website. Further, whilst every effort will be made to ensure that information on the website is accurate and correct, no warranty or guarantee is given by conferenceTM as to the accuracy of such information, and no liability will be accepted for loss or damage arising out of the use of such information.

##### _Changes to this Privacy Policy_  

conferenceTM may edit this policy from time to time. 

Use of this site constitutes acceptance of our Privacy Policy and Terms Of Service
